Zack, Arnold Arbitration Files 5512
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Scott Paper Co. - Tauton, City of. (Box 20)
  - Strand Lanes and Un. Bros. of Carpenter, Local 3108, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Superior Hat Tanning Co. and Leather Workers Internat'l Unions, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Syracuse University and Service Employees, Local 200, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Target Leasing, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - City of Taunton and Taunton Fire Fighters Union, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Teleflex, Inc. - Two Guys-Vornado, Inc.. (Box 21)
  - Teleflex, Inc. and U.A.W. Local 1039, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Teledyne Rodney Metals and, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Trayer Furniture Corp. and U.F.W.A. Local 154, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Threadwill Tap & Die Co. and UE Local 274, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Threadwill Tap & Dye Co. Greenfield, Mass. And I.U.E. Local 218, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Toms River Arbitration, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Torrington Co. and UAW Local 1645, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Torrington Company -and- UAW, Local 1645, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Trailways of N.E. and Amalg. Transit Union. Div. 1318, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Trailways of N.E., Inc. and Amalg. Transit Union, Div. 1318, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Trailways of N.E. Inc. and Amalg. Transit Union, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Trailways of N.E. and Amalg. Transit Union, Div. 1318, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Triangle Publications, Inc. and Newspaper Guild of Gr. Phila, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Triangle Mfg. Co. and UFWA Local 75, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority and District Council 37, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Two Guys and Retail Clerk Local 1358, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Tru-Connector Corp. and I.U.E. Local 257, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Two Guys From Harrison and Retail Clerks Un. Local 1360, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Two Guys-Vornado, Inc. and Retail Clerks, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Union Carbide Corp. - Westhill Cent. Sch. Dist.. (Box 22)
  - Union Carbide Corp. and Chemical & Crafts Union, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - United Parcel Service and Int. Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Envelope Company and, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Universal Show Factory Sanford, Maine, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Upper Merion, Pa. School Bd. And N.E.A., 1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Van Ham Pattern & Foundry Co. and Pattern Makers League of NA, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Valor Manufacturing Co. and Amalgamated Clothing Wkrs. Union, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Venezuelan Air Lines and I.A.M., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Vermont Tap & Die Co. and U.S.W.A. Dist. No. 1, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Vornado, Inc. and Retail Clerks Local 1371, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Yorktown, Heights Teachers and Yorktown Faculty Association, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - S.D. Warren Co. and U.P.P., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Warrick School Comm. And AFSCME Local 70, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Watchung Hills Bd. Of Ed. And Teachers Assoc., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Waterbury Bd. Of Ed. And Teachers Assoc., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Waterbury Bd. Of Ed. And Waterbury Teachers Assoc., 1970 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - West End & Hub Spring Co. and United Furniture Workers, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Westhill Central School District and Westhill District Faculty Assoc., 1969 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Westerly, RI Teachers Assoc. - Zoological Soc. of Philadelphia and Misc. (l ff). (Box 23)
  - Westerly, R.I. Teachers' Assoc. and School CTE., 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Weyerhaeuser Co. and Int. Bro., 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - WHDH, Inc. and Radio & TV Broadcast Engrs. Local 1228, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Whelan Drug Company and Retail & Whsle Dept. Stores, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Town of Whitman -and Police Association, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Worthington Marine & Indus. Products and U.S.W.A. Local 6911, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Woodbridge Teachers Union and Woodbridge Board of Education, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Youngstown Bd. Of Ed. And Ohio Ed. Assoc., 1971 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Youngstown Ohio, Education Binders, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Youngstown Bd. Of Education -and- Youngstown (Ohio) Educ, Assoc., 1972 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Misc., 1969 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Zoological Soc. Of Phila. -and- Phila Zoological Employees, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 12)